

Contact

Berlin, Germany

+4917661652846

in /sergio-pizarro-segovia

sergio.pizarroseg@gmail.com

/SergioPizarro

Languages

Spanish - Mother tongue

English - Professional working proficiency

German - B1

Skills

<div class="Skills"> <|i> HTML</|i> CSS Javascript <Ii> SASS</Ii> Bootstrap Stimulus Ruby on Rails SQL Heroku Cloudinary

Sergio Pizarro

Fullstack-developer

Profile

After graduating with a degree in Industrial Engineering from the Diego Portales University in Santiago de Chile, I moved to Berlin to improve my language skills and intercultural competences. I just completed an intensive web-developer full-stack bootcamp at Le Wagon. During this program I specialized primarily in backend development, but continuing to learn new technologies like React.

Education

Le Wagon

04/2022 - 06/2022

Web-Developer full-stack

9-week full-time intensive coding bootcamp learning HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript ES6, SQL, git, GitHub, Heroku and Ruby on Rails.

Diego Portales University

03/2013 - 03/2019

Industrial Engineering

Industrial Engineering is an engineering profession that is focused on the optimization of complex processes, systems, or organizations by developing, improving and implementing integrated systems of people, finances, knowledge, information and equipment.

Experience

Edipro

01/2019 - 06/2019

Internship

Creation and implementation of a tool to be used in the cloud with the function of obtaining multiplatform data with Google App Script. Analysis of the obtained data to enhance the decision-making process with statisticaldescriptive schemes.

Vínculo **Empresarial**

06/2018 - 08/2018

Internship

Modeling of truck loading processes with Bizagi including the simulation of multiple solutions with Arena simulator, in order to reach the optimal method according to the company's interests.

Projects

We-Pick

Ruby on Rails

Website to take desicions when you want to decide for something to do with your friends. I worked on the routes, cloudinary, controls, models, the seed for the database, CRUD and some SQL with Active Records.

Rent a plant app

Ruby on Rails

Website to rent a plants depending on the city that you are. I worked in the routes, models, controls, deploy to Heroku, cloudinary, database creation, schemas and migrations, seed for the database.